<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on AWK/</title>
    <link>http://awk.codeberg.page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on AWK/</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Abdallah Khalaf (CC)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:42:34 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://awk.codeberg.page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>projects</title>
      <link>http://awk.codeberg.page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awk.codeberg.page/projects/</guid>
      <description> asciid image to ASCII art convertor mapss pattern based password generator marss RSS feed generator for static sites </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://awk.codeberg.page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awk.codeberg.page/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey i&amp;rsquo;m Abdallah Khalaf, i&amp;rsquo;m a self-thaught computer programmer and electronics technician, i got interested in programming couple of years ago and started tinkering and writing programs for different platforms, ranging from web browsers to 16-bit microcontrollers. this website is an attempt to share things i discover or learn, projects, personal ideas and some opinions.
contact info: contact.awkcodes@gmail.com twitter github codeberg </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grayscale</title>
      <link>http://awk.codeberg.page/posts/grayscale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:42:34 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awk.codeberg.page/posts/grayscale/</guid>
      <description>i find with grayscale images a unique aesthetic that is distinct from full-color images. especially images that are referring to something old where it convey sense of timelessness or nostalgia, as black and white photography has a rich history that dates back to the origins of photography itself.
most photo editors had black and white theme, but i like to do things the hard way, so here is an attempt to do it in JavaScript and html canvas API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Mirroring</title>
      <link>http://awk.codeberg.page/posts/git-mirroring/git-mirroring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:08:05 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awk.codeberg.page/posts/git-mirroring/git-mirroring/</guid>
      <description>intro git mirroring is a process of replicating a repository from one location to another one. to ensure that there are multiple copies of the repository available for use when needed. these mirrors can be used as backups, or to ensure accessing repositories easily for large distributed teams.
of course, git mirroring can be done manually by copying the repo files to other locations, but this approach will make it difficult to keep the copies in sync.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
